resy.com 2015-02-22

# Legal - RESY | Grab a seat.

Resy Networks, Inc. Privacy Policy  
This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Resy Networks, Inc. (“Resy”, “we”, “our” or “us”) on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on the Resy mobile application (the “Application”); www.resy.com (the “Site”); Resy’s pages, profiles, or accounts on third party social networking services (“Social Networking Pages”), and the services, features, content or applications we offer (collectively with the Application, the Site, and the Social Media Pages, the “Services”). We receive information about you from various sources, including: (i) if you register for the Services, through your user account on the Services (your “Account”); (ii) your use of the Services generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?  
This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) gathered when you are using or accessing the Services. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to restaurants in the Resy network (“Restaurants”), or any other third party websites, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through the Services or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. Some examples of these Third Party Services are provided throughout this Privacy Policy, but please note that the examples may not be a complete list. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

What Information Do We Collect?  
The information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and continue to operate the Services. In connection with certain aspects of the Services, we may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information. We collect the following types of information from our users.

Account Information: When you create an Account, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your name, password, email address, and the login information you provide through Facebook Connect, OAuth, or other authentication mechanism. If you sign in to the Services through a Third Party Service, you understand some content and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into your account with us, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy; for example, if you log into the Services through Facebook, information in your Facebook profile may be used to “pre-populate” your Services profile.

You acknowledge that some of the information we collect throughout the registration process may be personal to you, and that by creating an Account and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore may not be anonymous. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or assist you with your Account, such as when you need to recover your password. You may unsubscribe from some of these messages through your Account settings, although we, regardless, reserve the right to contact you when we believe it is necessary, such as for account recovery purposes. 

Information About Your Bookings on the Services: When you use the Services, including without limitation to make a reservation with a Restaurant (“Reservation”), we collect and store information related to the Reservations you make (“Booking Behavior”), both for your later access and review, as well as for our use in making the Services a better experience for you. Booking Behavior may include, for example, what Reservations you have made and what types of restaurants you make Reservations with, as well as aggregate information about your use of the Services, such as your total number of Reservations and the average amount spent per Reservation.

User Content: Some features of the Services allow you to provide content to the Services, such as when you post reviews or provide written comments. All content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your account. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties in a manner that does not reveal Personal Information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

Financial Information: We do not currently collect financial information, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information); that information is collected and stored by our third party payment processing company (the “Payment Processor”), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy. 

IP Address Information, Device Information, and Other Information Collected Automatically: *We automatically receive and record information from your web browser and/or mobile device when you interact with the Services, including your IP address information. This information is used for fighting spam or malware and also to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with the Services (e.g., what links you have clicked on). *Generally, the Services automatically collect usage information, such as the number and frequency of users accessing the Services. Except as otherwise provided herein (see, for example our section on information shared with Restaurants), we only use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of the Services so that we can analyze and improve them. *We may collect some device-specific information if you access the Services using a mobile device. Device information may include but is not limited to unique device identifiers, network information, and hardware model, as well as information about how the device interacts with our Services. 

Email, SMS Text, and Push Notification Communications: We may communicate with you via email, SMS text message (to the extent you permit us to do so), or through the Application’s push notification feature. For example, we may send you a reminder via text message about an upcoming reservation the night before your reservation. You can choose to opt out of certain communications; however, if you do so, you may not be able to take advantage of some of our Services’ best features. We may also receive a confirmation when you open an email, read a text message, or receive a push notification sent by us or other users (including without limitation, the Restaurant with which you’ve made a Reservation). We use this confirmation to improve our customer service. 

Location Information: Some of our Services may include features based on users’ actual locations and may report on users’ current locations (“Location-Based Services”). To the extent you voluntarily opt in to use Location-Based Services, we may collect and store information about your location at the time you use those Location-Based Services. This information can come from a variety of sources depending on the client you use to access the Services; for example, a mobile phone may report its GPS location at the time Location-Based Services are used. We use this information to customize and enhance your experience on the Services, such as by showing you Restaurants with reservations available that are located near you.

Information Regarding Your Social Networks: Occasionally, you can use your Account on our Services to interact with your accounts on other services, such as Facebook or Twitter. In addition to using your third party account credentials to sign in to the Services, you can access posting and sharing tools on the Services, including a “share” button that allows you to post information to your social networks outside of the Services (“Share”). For example, after making a reservation on Resy, you can Share information about that reservation with your Facebook friends or Twitter followers. Please note that these tools may be operated by Third Party Services. 

By using these tools, you acknowledge that some Third Party Account Information may be transmitted into your Account with us, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy. Additionally, when you use one of these sharing tools, the Third Party Service that operates the tool may be collecting information about your browser or online activity through its own tracking technologies and subject to its own privacy policy. Lastly, when you use these tools, some of your information from the Services (such as the reservation information you selected to Share) may be shared with the Third Party Service and others. Therefore, we encourage you to read the privacy policies and other policies of the social networks you use in connection with the Services. 

Information From Your Correspondence With Us: If you contact us directly, for example to obtain customer service or technical support, we may collect the information you provide to us, such as your contact information. We will use such information to correspond with you and/or improve our Services.

Aggregate Information: We collect statistical information about how both unregistered and registered users, collectively, use the Services (“Aggregate Information”). Some of this information is derived from Personal Information. This statistical information is not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account, your web browser, or your mobile device.

How, and With Whom, Is My Information Shared?  
The Services are designed to help you share information with others. As a result, some of the information generated through the Services is shared publicly or with third parties.

Public Information About Your Activity on the Services: Some of your activity on and through the Services is public by default. This may include, but is not limited to, content you have posted publicly on the Application or otherwise through the Services. 

Registered users may have some of this information associated with their Accounts. Unregistered users will not have this association, but information concerning their use of the Services (such as what pages they have visited and, to the extent they have opted in to Location-Based Services, where they are located and where they access the Services) may be tracked anonymously and stored by us. 

Please also remember that if you choose to provide Personal Information using certain public features of the Services, then that information is governed by the privacy settings of those particular features and may be publicly available. Individuals reading such information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge, and search engines may index that information. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in content that you create or information that you submit through the Services.

IP Address and Device Information:  
While we collect and store IP address and device-specific information, that information is not made public. We do at times, however, share this information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business, and as otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy. 

Information Shared With Restaurants: When you use the Services to make a Reservation, we may share some of your information with the applicable Restaurant. Due to the nature of the Services, this information will likely include Personal Information, such as your name and contact information, and may further include information generated by your use of the Services, such as your user rating (as provided by Restaurants you previously made Reservations with) and Booking Behavior, as well as Third Party Account Information accessible by us. By making a Reservation or otherwise asking us to make information available to a Restaurant, you consent to our sharing of such information with that particular Restaurant. 

Additionally, Restaurants may be able to search for users using certain criteria. If you match the criteria, the Restaurant may be able to view some of your information, including your Booking Behavior. For example, a Restaurant searching for users with a “five-star” user rating may see your profile in their search results if you have a five-star rating on the Services.

We will only share a limited amount of information with Restaurants, but we take no responsibility for any Restaurant’s actions with respect to or treatment of your information. 

Third Party Services: You may access Third Party Services through the Services, for example by clicking on links to those Third Party Services from within the Application (such as a link to a restaurant’s website) or by actively sharing content from the Services on your account on an outside social networking site. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these Third Party Services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those Third Party Services’ privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Services.

Location Information: If we share your location information in a way that would personally identify you, it will be solely in order to provide you with the Services, and we will not share such information without your consent. For example, if you book a reservation, we may share your location with the Restaurant starting approximately thirty (30) minutes prior to your reservation time, so that the Restaurant can tell whether you will be running late; however, we will not do this unless you expressly choose to use the feature by selecting it on your reservation confirmation page.

Aggregate Information: We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use our Services and their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how our Services interface with them. In addition, these third parties may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non Personal Information about you that they have independently developed or acquired. 

Email and Other Communications with Us: As part of the Services, you may occasionally receive email and other communications from us, such as communications relating to your Account. You will have the ability to opt out of any marketing or advertising communications, but we may still send you communications relating to your Account for purposes important to the Services, such as password recovery.

User Profile Information: User profile information including your name and other information you enter may be displayed to other users, such as Restaurants, to facilitate user interaction within the Services. 

Financial Information: As stated above, we do not currently collect financial information, as that information is collected and stored by our Payment Processor. However, we may from time to time request and receive some of your financial information from our Payment Processor for the purposes of completing transactions you have initiated through the Services, enrolling you in discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, protecting against or identifying possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

Information Shared with Our Agents: We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our “Agents”). We may need to share Personal Information with our Agents in order to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents.

Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others: We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as we reasonably believe is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention.

Information We Share With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

Is Information About Me Secure?  
Your Account information will be protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your Account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account.

We seek to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

We otherwise store all of our information, including your IP address information, using industry-standard techniques. We do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you that we store, Personal Information or otherwise.

What Information of Mine Can I Access?  
If you are a registered user, you can access information associated with your Account by logging into the Services. California Privacy Rights: Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 315 Park Avenue South, 16th Floor, NY, NY 10010.

How Can I Delete My Account?  
Should you ever decide to delete your Account, you may do so by emailing help@resy.com. If you terminate your Account, any association between your Account and information we store will no longer be accessible through your Account. However, given the nature of sharing on the Services, any public activity on your Account prior to deletion will remain stored on our servers and will remain accessible to the public.

What Choices Do I Have Regarding My Information?  
* You can use some of the features of the Services without registering, thereby limiting the type of information that we collect. *You can always opt not to disclose certain information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of some of our features. *You can delete your Account. Please note that we will need to verify that you have the authority to delete the Account, and activity generated prior to deletion will remain stored by us and may be publicly accessible. *You can opt out of some of the features on the Services (such as certain email communications), and you can choose not to opt in to other features (such as certain Location-Based Services or text message notifications). 

What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?  
We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Services or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

What If I Have Questions or Concerns?  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Services, please send us a detailed message to help@resy.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: May 11, 2014
